<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Script Terror</title>
    <link>https://voodoods.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Script Terror</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://voodoods.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://voodoods.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://voodoods.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Script Terror is a blog about web software development by Norman Steger.
Norman is a Software Engineer with a preference for JavaScript and TypeScript based technology stacks located in Regensburg, Germany. While also not shy of working on webservices in the backend, he is most enthusiastic about:
 user experience agile methodology test driven development behavior driven development  Currently he works as a consultant at Comsysto Reply GmbH, where he helps customers in industries like automotive, telecommunications, insurance, transportation or finance to build digital experiences for tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Testing in React is superior to Angular</title>
      <link>https://voodoods.github.io/blog/2021-10-18_testing-react-vs-angular/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://voodoods.github.io/blog/2021-10-18_testing-react-vs-angular/</guid>
      <description>Or: Why I hate unit testing in Angular Every good article needs to start with a click-baity title that polarizes the masses. And thus I can already feel an army of enfuriated Angular developers breathing down my neck as I write these lines.
Since you naturally practice TDD, bcause you&amp;rsquo;re a responsible professional (even though you probably don&amp;rsquo;t), you will know that testing logic Angular down to the method can be a pain in the ass.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
